Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Central Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Central Files
  - 1998/1999
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Searches
        - Music (Box 402)
        - Public Policy Studies (Box 402)
        - Research (Box 402)
        - University Library (Box 402)
        - University Relations (Box 402)
        - Vice President for Communications [PR Restricted until July 1, 2029 ] (Box 402)
      - Secretary of the University: Budget (Box 402)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA)
        - General, 3 folders (Box 402)
        - Budget (Box 402)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 402)
      - Sexual Orientation (Box 402)
      - Space
        - General (Box 402)
        - Michigauma (Box 505)
      - Spencer Foundation (Box 402)
      - Students
        - General (Box 403)
        - Deceased (Box 403)
        - Cantor, Courtney (Box 505)
        - Grievances (Box 505)
        - Reese, Jeffrey (Box 505)
      - Student Affairs
        - General (Box 403)
        - Appointments (Box 403)
        - Budget (Box 403)
      - Substance Abuse (Box 403)
      - Surveys (Box 403)
      - Sweatshop
        - General (Box 403)
        - Sweatshop-Legal (Box 505)
      - Sympathy (Box 403)
      - Task Forces (Box 403)
      - Teaching Assistants (Box 403)
      - Technology Transfer (Box 403)
      - Thurnau Professorships (Box 403)
      - Tuition and Fees
        - General (Box 403)
        - MSA Fees (Box 505)
      - Turkish Chair (Box 403)
      - Undergraduate Education (Box 403)
      - Unit Assessment (Box 403)
      - University Library
        - General, 2 folders (Box 403)
        - Appointments (Box 403)
        - Budget (Box 403)
      - University of Michigan, Information about (Box 403)
      - University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI) (Box 403)
      - University Press (Box 403)
      - University Relations
        - General (Box 403)
        - Vice President: Budget (Box 403)
      - Website Inquiries
        - Personnel (Box 403)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Wiesner Policy Symposium (Box 403)
      - Whitaker Foundation (Box 403)
      - Women
        - General, 2 folders (Box 403)
        - Stewart, Abigail (Box 403)
      - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation (Box 404)
      - Working Group on Graduate and Professional Studies (Box 404)
      - Working Group: Interdisciplinary (Box 404)
      - Working Group on Organization (Box 404)
      - Working Group on Research (Box 404)
      - Working Group on Undergrad Teaching (Box 404)
      - Year of Humanities and Arts (YOHA) (Box 404)
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, School of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 404)
        - Appointments (Box 404)
        - Budget (Box 404)
        - Budget Conference (Box 404)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 404)
      - Art and Design, School of
        - General (Box 404)
        - Appointments (Box 404)
        - Budget (Box 404)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 404)
      - Business Administration, School of
        - General (Box 404)
        - Appointments (Box 404)
        - Budget (Box 404)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 404)
        - Students (Box 505)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2109 ]
      - Dearborn Campus (Box 404)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General (Box 404)
        - Appointments (Box 404)
        - Budget (Box 404)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 404)
      - Education, School of
        - General (Box 404)
        - Appointments (Box 404)
        - Budget (Box 404)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 404)
      - Engineering, College of (Box 405)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 405)
        - Budget (Box 405)
        - Budget Conference (Box 405)
        - Faculty Appointments, 2 folders (Box 405)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 405)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Flint Campus
        - General (Box 405)
        - Chancellor Search (Box 505)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Information, School of
        - General (Box 405)
        - Budget (Box 405)
        - Personnel (Box 405)
        - Regents' Communication (Box 405)
      - Kinesiology Division
        - General (Box 405)
        - Budget (Box 405)
        - Personnel (Box 405)
        - Regents' Communication (Box 405)
      - Law School
        - General (Box 405)
        - Admissions (Box 505)
        - Appointments (Box 405)
        - Budget (Box 405)
        - Budget Conference (Box 405)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 405)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - General, 3 folders (Box 405)
        - Budget (Box 405)
        - Faculty Appointments (Box 406)
        - Faculty Grievances (Box 406)
        - Faculty Recruiting (Box 406)
        - Ocean Drilling Program (Box 406)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 406)
      - Medical School
        - General, 3 folders (Box 406)
        - Budget (Box 406)
        - Faculty Appointments (Box 406)
        - Regents' Communication (Box 406)
      - Music, School of
        - General (Box 406)
        - Appointments (Box 406)
        - Budget (Box 406)
        - Grievances (Box 505)
        - Regents' Communication (Box 406)
        - Stein, Louise (Box 505)
      - Natural Resources and the Environment, School of
        - General (Box 406)
        - Budget (Box 406)
        - Personnel (Box 406)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 406)
      - Nursing, School of level3
        - General (Box 406)
        - Appointments (Box 406)
        - Budget (Box 406)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 406)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - General (Box 407)
        - Budget (Box 407)
        - Faculty and Appointments (Box 407)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 407)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General (Box 407)
        - Appointments (Box 407)
        - Budget (Box 407)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 407)
      - Public Policy, School of
        - General (Box 407)
        - Appointments (Box 407)
        - Budget (Box 407)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 407)
      - Rackham Graduate School
        - General (Box 407)
        - Appointments (Box 407)
        - Center for Child and Family Complaint (Box 505)
        - Budget (Box 407)
        - Budget Conference (Box 407)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Recreational Sports
        - Budget (Box 407)
        - Budget Conference (Box 407)
      - Social Work, School of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 407)
        - Appointments (Box 407)
        - Budget (Box 407)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 407)
    - Chronological File
      - September 1998-August 1999, 5 folders (Box 487)
  - 1999/2000
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Academic Affairs
        - General (Box 407)
          [Executive records restricted until July 01, 2020 ]
        - Budget (Box 407)
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 407)
      - Academic Computing Advising Committee (Box 407)
      - Academic Outreach-Budget (Box 407)
      - Academic Policy Committee (APC) (Box 407)
      - Academic Program Group (APG), 4 folders (Box 407)
      - Academic Program Group Development Subcommittee (Box 407)
      - Academic Program Group: Research (Box 407)
      - Accreditation
        - General, 3 folders (Box 408)
        - Self-Study Report for Institutional Reaccreditation, 2 folders (Box 408)
      - Admissions
        - General, 2 folders (Box 408)
        - Budget (Box 408)
        - Granger, Daniel (Box 505)
          [Patient/client records restricted until July 01, 2100 ]
        - Student Inquiries (Box 505)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2085 ]
      - Advisory Committee on University Budgets (ACUB) (Box 408)
      - Alumni (Box 408)
      - American Council on Education (Box 408)
      - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 408)
      - Appropriations (Box 408)
      - Arboretum (Box 408)
      - Arthur Miller (Box 408)
      - Articles (Box 408)
      - Arts of Citizenship (Box 408)
      - Associate Provost, 3 folders (Box 408)
      - Association of American Colleges and Universities (Box 409)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 409)
      - Association of American University Professors (Box 409)
      - Athletics
        - General, 2 folders (Box 409)
        - Legal (Box 505)
        - Recreational Sports (Box 409)
      - Atlas Project (Box 409)
      - Audits (Box 409)
        [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2030 ]
      - Awards
        - General (Box 409)
        - MAGB (Box 409)
      - Benefits (Box 409)
      - Bentley Historical Library
        - General (Box 409)
        - Budget (Box 409)
      - Biomedical Research (Box 409)
      - Budget
        - General, 4 folders (Box 409)
        - State Budget Request (Box 409)
        - Budget and Planning (Box 409)
      - Business and Finance
        - General (Box 409)
        - Budget (Box 409)
      - Calendar (Box 409)
      - Campaign Planning (Box 409)
      - Capital Commitment Forms (Box 409)
      - Capital Projects (Box 409)
      - Carnegie Foundation (Box 409)
      - Centers: General (Box 409)
      - Center for the Continuing Education of Women (CEW): Budget (Box 410)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT)
        - General (Box 410)
        - Budget (Box 410)
      - Charter Schools (Box 410)
      - Clements Library
        - General (Box 410)
        - Budget (Box 410)
        - Search (Box 410)
      - Clinical Track (Box 410)
      - Commencement (Box 410)
      - Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty (CESF) (Box 410)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 6 folders (Box 410)
      - Communications (Box 410)
      - Community Relations (Box 410)
      - Community Service and Learning
        - General (Box 410)
        - Appointments (Box 410)
      - Continuing Education for Women, Center for (CEW) (Box 410)
      - Copyright (Box 410)
      - Corporate Relations (Box 410)
      - Delegation of Authority (Box 410)
      - Detroit (Box 410)
      - Detroit Observatory, 2 folders (Box 410)
      - Development (Box 410)
      - Development, Vice President for (Box 410)
      - Distance Learning (Box 410)
      - Distinguished University Professorships (Box 411)
      - Diversity (Box 411)
      - Dual Careers (Box 411)
      - Economic Forecasting, 2 folders (Box 411)
      - Enrollment (Box 411)
      - Environment, Council on the (Box 411)
      - Ethics (Box 411)
      - Events (Box 411)
      - Executive Officers
        - General (Box 411)
        - Appointments (Box 411)
      - Executive Vice President for Medical Affairs (EVPMA) (Box 411)
      - Faculty
        - General, 2 folders (Box 411)
        - Appointments (Box 411)
      - Faculty Compensation (Box 411)
      - Faculty Work-Life Study Report (Box 411)
      - Fathom (Box 411)
      - Financial Reports, 7 folders (Box 411)
      - Finance
        - General (Box 412)
        - Budget (Box 412)
      - Financial Aid
        - General (Box 412)
        - Budget (Box 412)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Fleming Building (Box 412)
      - Flexible Benefits (Box 412)
      - Ford Library (Box 412)
      - Ford Motor Company (Box 412)
      - Ford Nuclear Reactor (Box 412)
      - Foundations: General (Box 412)
      - Funding
        - General, 2 folders (Box 412)
        - Appointments (Box 412)
      - "Gay Class" (English 317: "How to Be Gay") (Box 412)
      - General Counsel
        - General (Box 505)
        - Budget (Box 412)
      - Gifts, 2 folders (Box 412)
      - Global Change (Box 412)
      - Government Relations (Box 412)
      - Government: State (Box 412)
      - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) Negotiations, 2 folders (Box 412)
      - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) Tuition Assessment (Box 412)
      - Health Science Council (Box 412)
      - Health Services Research Initiative (Box 412)
      - Health System
        - General (Box 412)
        - General Counsel (Box 505)
      - Higher Education (Box 412)
      - Honorary Degree (Box 412)
      - Hospital Executive Board, 7 folders
        - Folder 1 (Box 412)
        - Folders 2-7 (Box 413)
      - Housing (Box 413)
      - Human Resources and Affirmative Action
        - General (Box 413)
        - Personnel (Box 413)
      - Indemnification (Box 413)
      - Indirect Cost Recovery (ICR) (Box 413)
      - Information Technology Division (ITD)
        - General, 3 folders (Box 413)
        - Budget (Box 413)
        - Vice President for (Box 413)
      - Institutes
        - General (Box 413)
        - Institute for Continuing Legal Education (ICLE)
          - General (Box 413)
          - Budget (Box 413)
        - Institute of Gerontology (Box 413)
        - Institute for Social Research
          - General (Box 413)
        - Budget (Box 414)
        - Personnel (Box 414)
      - Intellectual Property (IPO) (Box 414)
      - Interdisciplinary (Box 414)
      - International
        - General (Box 414)
        - Appointments (Box 414)
        - Campus Committee on International Affairs, 4 folders (Box 414)
          - International programs for School of Nursing and selected universities memorandums, 1998
            [Executive records restricted until July 1, 2020 ]
        - International Institute External Review (Box 414)
      - Keck Proposal (Box 414)
      - Kellogg Foundation (Box 414)
      - Knight Collaborative Engagement (Box 414)
      - Life Sciences, 3 folders (Box 414)
      - Living/Learning (Box 415)
      - Marshall Scholarship (Box 415)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. (Box 415)
      - Master Plan (Box 415)
      - Media Rights
        - General (Box 415)
        - Search (Box 415)
      - Media Union
        - General, 2 folders (Box 415)
        - Budget (Box 415)
      - Medical Affairs (Box 415)
      - Medical Center (Box 415)
      - Mellon Foundation (Box 415)
      - Memberships (Box 415)
      - Michigan Campus Compact (Box 415)
      - Michigan College University Partnership (Box 415)
      - Michigan Health Corporation, 4 folders (Box 415)
      - Michigan Student Assembly (MSA) (Box 415)
      - Microelectromechanical Systems (MEMS) (Box 415)
      - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Actives (MUCIA) (Box 415)
      - Millennium (Box 415)
      - Minorities (Box 415)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 415)
      - Multicultural Academic Affairs
        - General (Box 415)
        - Initiatives (Box 415)
      - Museum of Art
        - General (Box 415)
        - Budget (Box 415)
      - Musical Society (Box 415)
      - (NASULGC) (Box 416)
      - National Science Foundation (NSF)
        - General (Box 416)
        - Neuroscience (Box 416)
      - News and Information, 2 folders (Box 416)
      - New Student Programs
        - General (Box 416)
        - Budget (Box 416)
      - Note Taking (Commercial)
        - General (Box 416)
        - Working Group (Box 416)
      - Office of Academic Affairs (OAA) 8+1, 2 folders (Box 416)
      - Outreach (Box 416)
      - Parking (Box 416)
      - Partnerships (Box 416)
      - Pathways, 3 folders (Box 416)
      - Peer Institutions (Box 416)
      - Personnel
        - General (Box 416)
        - Appointments (Box 416)
      - Pew (Box 416)
      - Police (Box 416)
      - President's Advisory Group (PAG) (Box 416)
      - President's Advisory Committee on Women's Issues (PACWI) (Box 416)
      - President's Council: State (Box 416)
      - President's Office
        - General (Box 416)
        - Budget (Box 416)
      - Primary Research Scientists (PRS) (Box 416)
      - Professoriate (Box 416)
      - Promotions
        - General (Box 416)
        - Appointments (Box 416)
      - Proposals, 4 folders (Box 417)
      - Provost's Council on Student Honors (PCSH) (Box 417)
      - Provost's Faculty Initiative Program (PFIP) (Box 417)
      - Psychology
        - General (Box 417)
        - Appointments (Box 417)
        - Student (Box 505)
      - Public Goods (Box 417)
      - Regents
        - General (Box 417)
        - Communications, 4 folders (Box 417)
      - Registrar
        - General (Box 417)
        - Budget (Box 417)
        - Statistics (Box 417)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Requests (Box 417)
      - Research
        - General Folders 1-2 (Box 417)
        - General Folder 3 (Box 418)
        - Budget (Box 418)
        - Personnel Grievance (Box 418)
        - Reproductive Science Director Search (Box 418)
      - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC)
        - General (Box 418)
        - Officer Education Program-Air Force (Box 418)
        - Officer Education Program-Army (Box 418)
        - Officer Education Program-Navy (Box 418)
      - Residency (Box 505)
      - Résumés (Box 418)
      - Retirement (Box 418)
      - Rhodes Scholarship (Box 418)
      - "Road Scholars" (Box 418)
      - Safety Committee (Box 418)
      - Salary
        - General (Box 418)
        - Exceptions (Box 418)
      - Scholarships and Fellowships (Box 418)
      - Science and Policy (Box 418)
      - Science and Technology (Box 418)
      - Sea Grant (Box 418)
      - Searches
        - Art and Design, 3 folders (Box 418)
        - Communication (Box 418)
        - Dearborn (Box 418)
        - Education (Box 418)
        - General (Box 418)
        - Information (Box 418)
        - Media Union (Box 418)
        - Music (Box 418)
      - Secretary of the University: Budget (Box 418)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA)
        - General, 3 folders (Box 418)
        - Budget (Box 418)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 418)
      - Sexual Orientation (Box 419)
      - Sloan Pre-tenure Leave Fellowship Program (Box 419)
      - Space
        - General (Box 419)
        - Recruitment and Retention (Box 419)
          [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2100 ]
      - Spencer Foundation (Box 419)
      - Strategic Planning (Box 419)
      - Students
        - General, 2 folders (Box 419)
        - Deceased (Box 419)
        - General Counsel (Box 505)
        - Grievances (Box 505)
        - Michigauma (Box 419)
      - Student Affairs
        - General (Box 419)
        - Budget (Box 419)
        - Grievances (Box 419)
      - Substance Abuse
        - General, 2 folders (Box 419)
        - Personnel (Box 419)
      - Surveys (Box 419)
      - Sweatshop (Box 419)
      - Sympathy (Box 419)
      - Task Forces (Box 419)
      - Technology Transfer (Box 419)
      - Thurnau Professorships (Box 419)
      - Tuition and Fees (Box 419)
      - Undergraduate Education (Box 419)
      - University Library
        - General (Box 419)
        - Budget (Box 419)
        - Searches (Box 419)
      - University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI)
        - General (Box 419)
        - Personnel (Box 419)
      - University Press
        - General (Box 419)
        - Budget (Box 419)
      - University Relations
        - General (Box 419)
        - Vice President: Budget (Box 419)
      - Versity (Box 419)
      - Website Inquiries
        - General (Box 419)
        - Personnel (Box 419)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Whitaker Foundation (Box 419)
      - Wilson Foundation (Box 419)
      - Women
        - General, 2 folders (Box 419)
        - Appointments (Box 419)
      - Y2K (Box 419)
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, School of
        - General (Box 420)
        - Appointments (Box 420)
        - Budget (Box 420)
      - Art and Design, School of
        - General (Box 420)
        - Appointments (Box 420)
        - Budget (Box 420)
      - Business Administration, School of
        - General (Box 420)
        - Appointments (Box 420)
        - Budget (Box 420)
        - Davis Institute (Box 420)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Dearborn Campus
        - General (Box 420)
        - Appointments (Box 420)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General (Box 420)
        - Appointments (Box 420)
        - Budget (Box 420)
      - Education, School of
        - General (Box 420)
        - Appointments (Box 420)
        - Budget (Box 420)
      - Engineering, College of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 421)
        - Appointments (Box 421)
        - Budget (Box 421)
        - Murnane/Kapteyn (Box 421)
        - Personnel Grievances (Box 421)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 421)
      - Flint Campus
        - General Counsel (Box 505)
      - Information, School of
        - General (Box 421)
        - Appointments (Box 421)
        - Budget Conference (Box 421)
      - Kinesiology Division
        - General (Box 421)
        - Appointments (Box 421)
        - Budget (Box 421)
      - Law School
        - General (Box 421)
        - Budget (Box 421)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - General (3folders) (Box 421)
        - Budget (Box 421)
        - Faculty Appointments (Box 421)
        - Faculty Grievances (Box 422)
        - History of Art External Review (Box 422)
        - Recruitment and Retention (Box 422)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 422)
      - Medical School
        - General, 2 folders (Box 422)
        - Budget (Box 422)
        - Faculty Appointments (Box 422)
        - Recruitment and Retention (Box 422)
        - Regents' Communication (Box 422)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Music, School of
        - General (Box 422)
        - Appointments (Box 422)
        - Budget (Box 422)
        - Faculty Grievances (Box 422)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Natural Resources and the Environment, School of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 422)
        - Appointments (Box 422)
        - Budget (Box 422)
      - Nursing, School of
        - General (Box 422)
        - Appointments (Box 422)
        - Budget (Box 422)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - General (Box 422)
        - Appointments (Box 422)
        - Budget (Box 422)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 423)
        - Appointments (Box 423)
        - Budget (Box 423)
        - Self-Study Report, 2 volumes (Box 423)
      - Public Policy, School of
        - General (Box 423)
        - Appointments (Box 423)
        - Budget (Box 423)
        - General Counsel (Box 505)
      - Rackham Graduate School
        - General (Box 423)
        - Budget (Box 423)
        - Students (Box 505)
      - Social Work, School of
        - General (Box 423)
        - Appointments (Box 423)
        - Budget (Box 423)
    - Chronological Files, 1 folder
      - September-December 1999 (Box 487)
      - January-August, 2000 (Box 488)
  - 2000/2001
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Academic Affairs
        - General (Box 423)
          [Executive records restricted until July 01, 2021 ]
        - Budget (Box 423)
        - Personnel (Box 423)
          [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2031 ]
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Committee
        - General (Box 423)
        - Personnel (Box 423)
      - Academic Program Group (APG), 4 folders
        - Folders 1-3 (Box 423)
        - Folders 4 (Box 424)
      - Academic Program Group Development Subcommittee (Box 424)
      - Accreditation (Box 424)
      - Admissions
        - General, 2 folders (Box 424)
        - Student Grievances (Box 505)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2041 ]
      - Affiliation Agreements, 2 folders (Box 424)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 424)
      - Alumni
        - General (Box 424)
        - Budget (Box 424)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (AAAS) (Box 424)
      - American Association for Higher Education (AAHE) (Box 424)
      - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 424)
      - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS) (Box 424)